Solutions

### 

Solutions

Our solutions help K-12 districts manage student safety and well-being on school-provided technology.

Resources

### 

Resources

Access Gaggle’s library of resources on student safety, SEL, cyberbullying, student mental health, and other topics in education.

About Us

### 

About Us

Learn about our mission, how we’ve been supporting student safety for more than 20 years, the latest company updates, and how to contact us.

 Search   

Website Privacy Policy

==========================

**Last Updated: September 9, 2022**

Welcome to the company website of Gaggle.Net, Inc. (Gaggle).

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit http://www.gaggle.net (the “Company Site”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information. Please note: The information herein represents only the Company Site at https://www.gaggle.net and not Gaggle.Net, Inc. (“Gaggle”) Solutions (“Services”).

The Company Site is intended for a general audience. Although we may permit educators and parents to access Gaggle solutions through links provided on the Company Site, access to and use of Gaggle solutions is governed by separate agreements with customers and authorized users, including our [Student Data Privacy Notice](https://www.gaggle.net/student-data-privacy-notice?hsLang=en "Gaggle Student Data Privacy Notice"), [Terms & Conditions](https://www.gaggle.net/terms-conditions?hsLang=en), and [Service Level Agreement](https://www.gaggle.net/service-level-agreement?hsLang=en). In addition, this policy does not apply to information collected by us offline or through any other means or by any third party, including through application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Company Site.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use the Company Site. By accessing or using the Company Site, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see "Changes to this Privacy Policy"). Your continued use of the Company Site after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

**Children Under the Age of 13 and Student Education Records  
**The Company Site is not intended for children under 13 years of age or for use in connection with student education records. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13, or information that may comprise student education records, through the Company Site. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on the Company Site or on or through any of its features. In addition, regardless of age, you should never provide student education records on or through the Company Site. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent or any education records of a minor student through the Company Site, we will delete that information.

To learn more about our practices with respect to student information entered into Gaggle solutions, please refer to our [Student Data Privacy Notice](https://www.gaggle.net/student-data-privacy-notice?hsLang=en "Gaggle Student Data Privacy Notice").

**Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It  
**We collect several types of information from, and about, users of the Company Site, including information:

* By which you may be personally identified, such as name, employer, job title, postal address, email address, and telephone number (“personal information”)
* About your internet connection, the equipment you use to access the Company Site, and other usage details

We collect information:

* Directly from you when you voluntarily provide it to us by completing web forms on the Company Site, such as requests for marketing or other information
* Automatically as you navigate through the Company Site, such as usage details, IP addresses, operating systems, browser types, and information collected through automatic data collection technologies, including cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies
* That details your visits to the Company Site, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data, and the resources that you access and use on the Company Site
* Including records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you choose to contact us
* To help us estimate our audience size and usage patterns
* To recognize you when you return to the Company Site

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

Cookies (or browser cookies): A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting, you may be unable to access certain parts of the Company Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, the Company Site will issue cookies when you direct your browser to the Company Site.

Web Beacons: Pages of our Company Site and our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit us, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

**Third-Party Use of Tracking Technologies  
**The Company Site works with third parties when you use the Company Site and to perform services on our behalf. We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions, you should contact the responsible provider directly.

* **Act-On** allows us to track the activity of anonymous and known prospects coming to the Company Site.
* **AddThis** is a social bookmarking service integrated into the Company Site through the use of a web widget to allow visitors to easily share content.
* **Disqus** is a networked community platform that allows the Company Site to gain a feature-rich comment system complete with social network integration, advanced administration and moderation options, and other extensive community functions.
* **Google Analytics** is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of the Company Site, prepare reports on its activities, and share them with other Google services.
* **Service Cloud** is a customer service platform that allows the Company Site to create customer relationships that are meaningful, personal, and productive through the use of live chat.  

**How We Use Your Information  
**We use information that we collect about you, or that you provide to us while visiting the Company Site, including any personal information:

* To present the Company Site and its contents to you
* To provide you with information about solutions or services that you request from us or that may be relevant to you
* To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it
* To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection
* To notify you about changes to the Company Site or any of our solutions or services
* In any other way that we may describe when you provide the information
* For any other purpose with your consent  

**Disclosure of Your Information  
**We may disclose aggregated information about our visitors to the Company Site, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. Unless otherwise stated herein, we will not disclose to any third party personal information that we collect or that you provide unless you provide consent to do so. We may disclose your personal information:

* To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company’s assets
* To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including responding to any government or regulatory request
* To enforce or apply our Terms & Conditions or Service Level Agreement
* If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of our company, our customers, or others  

**Choice/Opt Out  
**The Company Site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service:

* You can send an email to [support@gaggle.net](mailto:support@gaggle.net)
* You can send mail to the following postal address: P.O. Box 735566, Dallas, TX 75373-5566
* You can call the following telephone number: 800-288-7750  

**Correcting and Updating Information  
**The Company Site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:

* You can send an email to [support@gaggle.net](mailto:support@gaggle.net)
* You can send mail to the following postal address: P.O. Box 735566, Dallas, TX 75373-5566
* You can call the following telephone number: 800-288-7750  

**Telephone Calls  
**Telephone calls to and from Gaggle may be recorded for training or monitoring purposes only.

**Trademarks  
**All trademarks, service marks, trade names, logos, and graphics (“Marks”) indicated on this site are registered trademarks of Gaggle, its affiliates, and/or licensors in the United States and other countries. You may not make any use of Gaggle Marks without the prior written consent of Gaggle.Net, Inc.

The company, solutions, and service names used on this website are for identification purposes only. All trademarks and registered trademarks are the properties of their respective owners.

**Changes to This Policy  
**It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you via a notice on the Company Site home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for periodically visiting the Company Site and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

**Contact Information  
**You can, and should, ask questions about this policy and our privacy practices, or feel free to report complaints. You should always feel free to contact us at:

Gaggle.net, Inc.  
5050 Quorum Drive  
Suite 700  
Dallas, TX 75254  
Phone:  (800) 288-7750  
Email: [support@gaggle.net](mailto:support@gaggle.net)

* 
* 
* [.png?width=80&height=80&name=IKEEPSAFE%20Logo%20-%20Family%20Education%20Rights%20%26%20Privacy%20Act%20(FERPA).png)](https://ikeepsafe.org/products/#ferpa)
* 

[Website Privacy Policy](https://www.gaggle.net/privacy-policy?hsLang=en) | [Student and Staff Data Privacy Notice](https://www-gaggle-net.sandbox.hs-sites.com/student-data-privacy-notice?hsLang=en) | Copyright © 2024 Gaggle.Net, Inc.
